Finding Aid for the Edward C. Weber Papers, 1949-2005
Edward C. Weber Papers
- Correspondence
  - Harvard Gay & Lesbian Review (Box 20)
  - Harvard Journal of Negro Affairs (Box 20)
  - Haskell, Gordon K. (re his autobiography, A Missionary Shachtmanite) (Box 20)
  - Hauben, Ronda (reference: Flint Sit-Down Strike, Sidney Fine) (Box 20)
  - Hawley, Nancy (re: Female Liberation Newsletter) (Box 20)
  - Haymarket Books (re: order for Maoism and the Soviet Union) (Box 20)
  - Hayward, Harry (reference: The Crisis in the CPUSA) (Box 20)
  - Heaton, Paul (re: Campaign for Equality) (Box 21)
  - Heatwave (London, England) (Box 21)
  - Heberling, David (reference: Terence Powderly) (Box 21)
  - Helaine Victoria Enterprises (re: postcard of Agnes Inglis) (Box 21)
  - Help (London) (Box 21)
  - Hellwig, David J. (reference: Black attitudes toward immigrants in the U.S.) (Box 20)
  - Hennacy, Ammon (Box 21)
  - Henry, Barbara (reference: Lesbian periodicals) (Box 21)
  - Heppel, Alan (reference: IWW during the 1918 trials) (Box 21)
  - Heraclitus (New South Wales) (re: Max Nomad) (Box 21)
  - Herald of Freedom (Zarephath, NJ) (Box 21)
  - Herman, Gordon L. (re: order for Night of Moons) (Box 21)
  - Hermon, Harry, M.D. (reference: sexual freedom movement) (Box 21)
  - Herrick, Mary Darrah (reference: Almeda Sperry) (Box 21)
  - Her-Self (Ann Arbor, MI) (Box 21)
  - Hersh, Robert (reference: images for Spanish Civil War pictorial history) (Box 21)
  - Hertzberg, Richard (reference: graphic leaflets of the 1960s) (Box 21)
  - Hill, Herbert (NAACP) (Box 21)
  - Hill, Peter (reference: movies about intentional communities and communes) (Box 21)
  - Highlander Folk School (Box 21)
  - Hillegas, Jan (re: Freedom Information Service) (Box 21)
  - Hilton, Robert Lee (Box 21)
  - Hinze, Virginia Neal (reference: German radicalism in Chicago: 1848-1920) (Box 21)
  - Historia y Sociedad (Mexico) (Box 21)
  - Historical Society of Michigan (Box 21)
  - Historical Society of Pennsylvania (re: Voltairine de Cleyre) (Box 21)
  - Hobby, Daniel T. (reference: role and ideology of labor organizers during the Progressive Era, 1900-1917) (Box 21)
  - Hobo Foundation (Box 21)
  - Hodder & Stoughton, Ltd. (re: Hard Travellin’ by Kenneth Allsop) (Box 21)
  - Hodges, Donald C. (re: publications of Philosophical Study of Dialectical Materialism) (Box 21)
  - Hodgins, Tina (reference: Frank Little) (Box 21)
  - Hoerder, Dirk (reference: general) (Box 21)
  - Hoffer, Dale C. (reference: American aviators in Spanish Civil War) (Box 21)
  - Hoglund, A. William (reference: Finnish represented in the ACPFB Papers) (Box 21)
  - Hogue, Jany (reference: Boletín de Información– CNT) (Box 21)
  - Hoisington, Wm. A., Jr. (reference: holdings of the Communist International) (Box 21)
  - Hokanson, Nels M. (reference: Swedes in the IWW) (Box 21)
  - Holbrook, Mrs. Stewart (re: donation of IWW materials) (Box 21)
  - Holden, Mrs. Edna M. (re: donation of Emma Goldman materials) (Box 21)
  - Holding, Richard (Box 21)
  - Holton, Dr. R. (reference: IWW in Britain) (Box 21)
  - Holy Family (Box 21)
  - Holzkampen, Charlot Associates and Communications (reference: Elizabeth Gurley Flynn) (Box 21)
  - Homegrown (Providence, RI) (Box 21)
  - Homosexuelle Initiative (Vienna, Austria) (Box 21)
  - Hook, Sidney (Box 21)
  - Hoover Institute on War, Revolution, and Peace (Box 21)
  - Hope, Warren (reference: Carlo Tresca) (Box 21)
  - Horn, Frances E. (re: wish to sell Joe Hill postcards) (Box 21)
  - Horn, Max (reference: Intercollegiate Socialist Society) (Box 21)
  - Horseshit Magazine (Hermosa Beach, CA) (Box 21)
  - Hotchkiss School, Edsel Ford Memorial Library (reference: holdings on homosexual materials) (Box 21)
  - Houle, Peter (Box 21)
  - Hovey Street Press (re: book order for Comrade George by Eric Mann) (Box 21)
  - Howell, Mary E. (reference: Commonwealth College) (Box 21)
  - Howes, Robert W. (reference: Latin American gay publications) (Box 21)
  - Howson, Embrey B. (reference: Jacob Coxey) (Box 21)
  - Hug, Heinz (Erich Mühsam, Der Arme Teufel) (Box 21)
  - Hughes, C. Alvin (reference: Southern Negro Youth Congress) (Box 21)
  - Human Rights Internet Reporter (Cambridge, MA) (Box 21)
  - Human Voice, The (Ann Arbor, MI) (Box 21)
  - Humanizing City Life (Worthington, OH) (Box 21)
  - Humphries, Martin (order for Searching for a Destination) (Box 21)
  - Hunt, Richard P. (reference: first observation of Labor Day) (Box 21)
  - Huntington, William S. (Communist Party activities in the United Mineworkers of America) (Box 21)
  - Hurley, Gerard (Box 21)
  - Hurley Books (re: purchase of Morrison Swift Papers; Moral Re-Armament) (Box 21)
  - Hutchinson, Earl (reference: blacks in Socialist organizations) (Box 21)
  - Huxley, Christopher V. (reference: English labor movement (Box 21)
  - Hyde, J. W. (Hobo songs and poems from the 1930s) (Box 21)
  - Hyde Park Socialist (London) (Box 21)
  - Hyperion Press (re: order for After You’re Out by Jay Young) (Box 21)
  - I. F. Stone’s Weekly (Box 21)
  - IFCO News (New York) (Box 21)
  - IMG Publications (International Marxist Group) (Box 22)
  - ISM Press (reference: photo of Elizabeth Gurley Flynn for publication) (Box 22)
  - Iglehart, Ruth (re: donation of 18th Convention of the Socialist Party) (Box 22)
  - Illeborg, Steen (reference: IWW) (Box 22)
  - Illini Review (from ECW re: pro-Sandinista movement on campus) (Box 22)
  - Illinois Labor History Society (Box 22)
  - Illinois State Historical Society (re: Edward Aveling letter) (Box 22)
  - Illustrated Paper (Mendocino, CA) (Box 22)
  - Imani (New York) (Box 22)
  - Immigrant Aid Society of Americas (Box 22)
  - Imprimis (Hillsdale, MI) (Box 22)
  - In a Nutshell (Chicago, IL) (Box 22)
  - In Magazine (Iowa City) (Box 22)
  - Independent, The (Secaucus, NJ) (Box 22)
  - Independent Socialist Press (Box 22)
  - Indiana Historical Society Library (Box 22)
  - Indiana State University (Eugene V. Debs Project) (Box 22)
  - Indiana University Library (re: New Left Notes) (Box 22)
  - Indigena (Box 22)
  - The Individualist (London) (Henry Meulen, Personal Rights Assocation) (Box 22)
  - Industrial Defense Bulletin (Toronto) (Box 22)
  - Industrial Unionist (Oldham, England) (Box 22)
  - Industrial Worker (Chicago) (Box 22)
  - Industrial Workers of the World (Box 22)
  - Informacny Materialy (Berlin, Germany) (Box 22)
  - Informat (West Berlin) (Box 22)
  - Information Centre for Polish Affairs (U.K.) (Box 22)
  - Ingham, John N. (reference: general) (Box 22)
  - Inglis, Katherine S. (Box 22)
  - Inner City Light (New York) (Box 22)
  - Inside Story (London) (Box 22)
  - Institut Municipal d’Historia de Barcelona (reference: Boletín de Información CNT-FAI) (Box 22)
  - Institute for Social Justice (Box 22)
  - Institute for the Study of Nonviolence Journal (Palo Alto, CA) (Box 22)
  - Institute for Workers’ Control (Nottingham, England) (Box 22)
  - Institute of Contemporary Arts (London) (Box 22)
  - Institute of the Black World (Atlanta, GA) (Box 22)
  - Institute on Religion and Democracy (Washington DC) (Box 22)
  - Instituto di Storia C.N.R. (Florence, Italy) (Box 22)
  - Instituto Lambda (Barcelona) (Box 22)
  - Instituto Lambda de Colombia (Bogotá) (Box 22)
  - Instituto Socialista di Studi Storici (Florence, Italy) (Box 22)
  - Insurgent (New York) (Box 22)
  - Integrity (Fort Valley, GA) (Box 22)
  - Intercontinental Press (New York) (Box 22)
  - International (London) (Box 22)
  - International Anarchism (Selby, England) (Box 22)
  - International Confederation for Disarmament and Peace (London) (Box 22)
  - International Defence and Aid Fund for Southern Africa (London) (Box 22)
  - International Humanist and Ethical Union (Utrecht, Holland) (Box 22)
  - International Institute of Social History (Amsterdam, Holland) (Box 22)
  - International Marxist Review (London) (Box 22)
  - International Revolution (Sweden) (Box 22)
  - International Socialism (Socialist Review Publishing Co.) (Box 22)
  - International Socialism (London) (Box 22)
  - International Socialist (formerly: Independent Socialist) (New York) (Box 22)
  - International Socialist Journal (Rome, Italy) (Box 22)
  - International Socialist Review (New York) (Box 22)
  - International Spartacist Tendency (New York) (Box 22)
  - International Times (London) (Box 22)
  - International Typographical Union (Box 22)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (Box 22)
  - International Worker (New York) (Box 22)
  - International Workers’ Party (New York) (Box 22)
  - Internationale Gesellschaft für Menschenrecht (West Germany) (Box 22)
  - Internationale Situationniste (Paris) (Box 22)
  - Interrogations (Torino, Italy) (Box 22)
  - Iran Solidarity Newsletter (Manchester, England) (Box 22)
  - Irish Gay Rights Movement (Dublin, Ireland) (Box 22)
  - Irish Liberation Press (Box 22)
  - Irons, Priscilla Long (reference: Mother Jones) (Box 22)
  - Isca, Valerio (Box 22)
  - Issues & Actions (New York) (Box 22)
  - It’s About Time/Lesbian Separatist Group (Seattle, WA) (Box 22)
  - JRS Productions (re: John Reed Story) (Box 22)
  - Jack, W. H. R., Mrs. (re: books for sale from late husband’s library) (Box 22)
  - Jackson, Robert (reference: John Francis Bray) (Box 22)
  - Jackson, Peter M. (re: sale of John Francis Bray letters) (Box 22)
  - Jacobs, Ron (reference: images for Weather Underground article) (Box 23)
  - Jacobson, Kristi A. (reference: Upton Sinclair’s The Jungle) (Box 23)
  - Jamaica Gaily News (Kingston, Jamaica) (Box 23)
  - Jamieson, K.I (reference: William Francis Barnard; William C. Owen) (Box 23)
  - Janus Society (Harrisburg, PA) (Box 23)
  - Jeansonne, Glen (reference: Militant right) (Box 23)
  - Jeffreys-Jones, R. (reference: U.S. industrial relations 1890-1910) (Box 23)
  - Jenner, Demila (reference: Lucy Parsons) (Box 23)
  - Jensen, Richard (reference: speeches by William D. Haywood) (Box 23)
  - Jericho (Portland, OR) (Box 23)
  - Jervey, Edward D. (reference: Elmina Slenker) (Box 23)
  - Jeune Taupe (Paris) (Box 23)
  - Jewish Liberation Project (New York) (Box 23)
  - Jewish Museum (re: their exhibit “The Dreyfus Affair”) (Box 23)
  - Jewish Right, The (Sierra Madre, CA) (Box 23)
  - Johanningsmeier, Ed (reference: William Z. Foster; Syndicalist League of North America) (Box 23)
  - John Birch Society (Box 23)
  - John Dos Passos Newsletter (Lawrence, KA) (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Charles T. (reference: 9th and early 20th century socialism and anarchism) (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Oakley (reference: various research topics) (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Paul R. (re: writings about homosexuality in the Bible) (Box 23)
  - Johnston, Margaret R. (reference: Elizabeth Freeman and Rebecca Shelley) (Box 23)
  - Johnston, Richard (reference: C.L. “Gunplay” Maxwell; IWW) (Box 23)
  - Join Hands (San Francisco, CA) (Box 23)
  - Jones, Ann (mother of Bob Brubaker) (Box 23)
  - Jones, Rev. Ashton B. (re: Koinonia Foundation) (Box 23)
  - Jones, Bill and Fran (Box 23)
  - Jones, Dr. Charles E. (reference: Black Panther Party) (Box 23)
  - Jones, Deborah (Box 23)
  - Jones, Derik (re: La Prensa) (Box 23)
  - Jones, Gary (reference: IWW and Bolshevik Revolution) (Box 23)
  - Jones, Jim P. (Box 23)
  - Jones, Katherine J. (reference: woman question among American socialists 1900-1920) (Box 23)
  - Jones, Maldwyn A. (reference: Robert Watchorn (Box 23)
  - Jones, Mark (Box 23)
  - Jones, R. W. (reference: Solidarity – UK) (Box 23)
  - Jones, Raymond (Box 23)
  - Joseph, D. George (reference: drug use in the U.S from 1920-1940) (Box 23)
  - Joughin, Louis (re: index to Sacco-Vanzetti articles in L’Adunata dei Refrattari) (Box 23)
  - Journal Gay Internacional (Sao Paulo, Brazil) (Box 23)
  - Journal of Female Liberation (Boston, MA) (Box 23)
  - Journal of Modern History (re: The Dreyfus Affair) (Box 23)
  - Journal of Psychedelic Drugs (Beloit, WI) (Box 23)
  - Journal on Political Repression (New York) (Box 23)
  - Judd, Richard (reference: Socialist Party in Ohio municipal politics, 1900-1920) (Box 23)
  - Juicy News (formerly Adam’s Apple Hardcore) (Fort Wayne, IN) (Box 23)
  - Julian Review (Box 23)
  - Jungblut, Gerd W. (Erich Mühsam; Der Arme Teufel) (Box 23)
  - K., Walter (Box 23)
  - Kahn, Lori (reference: Rosenberg case) (Box 23)
  - Kalamazoo Institute of Arts (re: loan of material for their exhibit, “Artists in Revolt”) (Box 23)
  - Kales, David A. (reference: history of Canadian Trotskyism) (Box 23)
  - Kalkanis, Nick (Box 23)
  - Kallman, Theodore P. (reference: Josiah Warren) (Box 23)
  - Kameny, Franklin E. (Box 23)
  - Kalaidjian, Walter (reference: leftist poets published in “little magazines” of the 1920s and 30s) (Box 23)
  - Kann, Kenneth (reference: Chicago labor movement to 1886) (Box 23)
  - Kansas State Historical Library (re: microfilming of anarchist and socialist periodicals) (Box 23)
  - Kaplan, Justin (reference: Lincoln Steffens) (Box 23)
  - Kaplow, Julian (3 folders) (Box 24)
  - Kaplowitz, Julian (Box 24)
  - Kapp, Yvonne (reference: Edward Aveling photograph for her biography of Eleanor Marx) (Box 24)
  - Kartemquin Films, Ltd. (reference: newsreel footage of Eugene Debs) (Box 24)
  - Kasano, Shigeru (reference: John Francis Bray) (Box 24)
  - Kaufman, Murray (reference: Eugene Debs scrapbooks in the Labadie Collection) (Box 24)
  - Kay, Tamara (reference: Ezra and Angela Heywood) (Box 24)
  - Keene, Judith (reference: Spain in the 1930s) (Box 24)
  - Keep Left (London) (Box 24)
  - Keil, Hartmut (reference: Robert Reitzel; German workers in the U.S.) (Box 24)
  - Keim, Willard (reference: Johann Most) (Box 24)
  - Keller, Charles (re: establishing a Labadie Art Collection) (Box 24)
  - Kelley, Ken (re: Ann Arbor Argus, Bret Eynon) (Box 24)
  - Kelley, Wm. D., Jr. (reference: sheet music for “We Have Fed You All a Thousand Years”) (Box 24)
  - Kelly, Andrea (reference: Spanish Civil War) (Box 24)
  - Kelvin, Morris (reference: William Morris) (Box 24)
  - Kennedy, Hubert (reference: John Henry Mackay) (Box 24)
  - Kennedy, Stetson (re: various donations including 1956 Hungarian newspapers) (Box 24)
  - Kennys Bookshops (re: sale of anarchist newspapers) (Box 24)
  - Kent State University (reference: seeking materials about May 4, 1970 events) (Box 24)
  - Kepner, Jim (Box 24)
  - Kerber, Gerry (reference: IWW, Centralia) (Box 24)
  - Kerr, Peter (re: referrals to librarians at Berkeley, WSHS, Temple) (Box 24)
  - Kessler, June (reference: Durruti) (Box 24)
  - Key List Mailing (San Francisco) (Box 24)
  - Khronika Press ( Chronicle of Human Rights in the U.S.S.R.) (Box 24)
  - Kick It Over (Toronto) (Box 24)
  - Kimmel, Michael S. (reference: Stephen Pearl Andrews, Moses Harmon, Ezra Heywood) (Box 24)
  - King, Arnie (prisoner letter) (Box 24)
  - King, Jean Ledwith (reference: John Pancner/Panzner) (Box 24)
  - Kirkup, James (Box 24)
  - Kleinberg, Judith G. (re: her term paper, “An In-Depth Study of the Underground Press of the 1960s”) (Box 24)
  - Klejment, Anne M. (reference: Port Huron Statement) (Box 24)
  - Klibaner, Irwin (reference: radical movements and their relationship to Negroes since the 1890s) (Box 24)
  - Klipsun (Bellingham, WA) (reference: photograph of Wesley Everest) (Box 24)
  - Knepper, Robert (re: donation) (Box 24)
  - Knieriem, Michael (reference: Carl de Haas) (Box 24)
  - Knight, Rolf (re: oral histories of Canadian working people) (Box 24)
  - Knueppel, Christoph (reference: George Schumm) (Box 24)
  - Koblenz, Leonard (reference: article he published in Hammer and Tongs in 1948) (Box 24)
  - Koga, Nancy (reference: propaganda of the Communists during the Spanish Civil War) (Box 24)
  - Kogan, Bernard (reference: Haymarket, esp. Schwab, Fielden and Neebe) (Box 24)
  - Koizumi, Takashi (reference: John Francis Bray) (Box 24)
  - Koka, Karen (Box 24)
  - Kommunistiche Korrespondenz (Berlin, West Germany) (Box 25)
  - Koontz, Alan P. (reference: Individual Action; The Struggle; Minus One; Ego; Emma Goldman) (Box 25)
  - Korcheck, Robert A. (reference: poetry of the Sacco-Vanzetti case; Matilda Rabinowitz) (Box 25)
  - Korn, Sarah (IWW women strikers at Lawrence and Patterson; Solidarity) (Box 25)
  - Kornbluh, Joyce (includes letters from Archie Green; Lee Furey; Royce Ferguson) (Box 25)
  - Kosmerick, Todd J. (reference: article on IWW for Labor’s Heritage) (Box 25)
  - Koszyk, Kurt (reference: Joseph Weydemeyer) (Box 25)
  - Kovach, Ronald (reference: Josiah Warren) (Box 25)
  - Kraft, Barbara S. (reference: Holt Papers; Ford Peace expedition) (Box 25)
  - Kramer, Aaron (Box 25)
  - Krammer, Arnold (reference: Spanish Civil War) (Box 25)
  - Kresge Art Museum (re: borrowing materials for their exhibit, “Prints of the French Revolution) (Box 25)
  - Krieger, Nancy (reference: Marie Equi) (Box 25)
  - Kropotkin Society (Box 25)
  - Kropotkin’s Lighthouse Publications (Box 25)
  - Krummel, D.W. (Box 25)
  - Krupp Comic Works (Box 25)
  - KU African, The (Lawrence, KS) (Box 25)
  - Kudzu, The (Jackson, MS) (Box 25)
  - Kupferberg, Tuli (Box 25)
  - Kwaida Publications (Box 25)
  - LSM Information Center (Box 25)
  - Labidee, H. R. (reference: Agnes Inglis mentioned in Ray Ginger’s The Bending Cross) (Box 25)
  - Labadie, Laurance (Box 25)
  - Labor: a Weekly Newspaper Owned by the Railroad Workers of the U.S. and Canada (Washington DC) (Box 25)
  - Labor Action and New International (New York) (Box 25)
  - Labor Historians Newsletter (Detroit?) (Box 25)
  - Labor History (New York) (Box 25)
  - Labor Museum and Learning Center of Michigan (re: Knights of Labor exhibit) (Box 25)
  - Labor Publications (Box 25)
  - Labor Research Association (Box 25)
  - Labor’s Heritage (Box 25)
  - Labour Movement Library and Archive, The (Arbejderbevaegelsens Bibliotek og Arkiv) (Box 25)
  - Labour Worker [changed title to Socialist Worker] (London) (Box 25)
  - Ladder, The (Box 25)
  - Lader, Lawrence (reference: Margaret Sanger) (Box 25)
  - LaGroc (Box 25)
  - Lahaeye, Jean-Francois (re: donation of La Gazette du Ringard de Banlieu) (Box 25)
  - Lahr, Oonagh (re: Walsh/Lahr Wobbly photos) (Box 25)
  - Laissez Faire Books (re: anarchist calendar) (Box 25)
  - Lakewood Library (reference: Home Colony; Washington State) (Box 25)
  - Lallement, Jimmy (re: French anarchist materials) (Box 25)
  - Lamarre, Jean (reference: 19th century French-Canadian immigration to the Midwest) (Box 25)
  - Lambda (Torino, Italy) (Box 25)
  - Lambda (Barcelona, Spain) (Box 25)
  - Lambert, Dennis K. (reference: Der Arme Teufel) (Box 25)
  - Lamont, Corliss (Box 25)
  - Lampião (Rio de Janeiro, Brazil) (Box 25)
  - Lancaster Independent Press (Box 25)
  - Langbord, Eva (re: donation of Emma Goldman materials) (Box 25)
  - Langbord, Sadie (Box 25)
  - Langston Hughes Society (Box 25)
  - La Lanterne Noir (France) (Box 25)
  - LaPorte, Thomas A. (Box 25)
  - Lappen, Henry (re: Black and Green; Clamshell Alliance) (Box 25)
  - Lasron, David R. (reference: Socialist Party, Socialist Labor Party, IWW of Ohio) (Box 25)
  - Lashof, Judith P. (Box 25)
  - Laskin, Joshua (reference: Marx Edgeworth Lazarus) (Box 25)
  - Latin America Review of Books (London) (Box 25)
  - Lavender & Red Union (Box 25)
  - Law Reform Review (Pasadena, CA) (Box 25)
  - Lawrence, Franklin (Box 25)
  - Lazarus, Louis (reference: Workers International Industrial Union) (Box 25)
  - Lazerow, Jama (reference: Boston labor in the mid 1890s) (Box 25)
  - League for Industrial Democracy (from ECW re: article about Grenada) (Box 25)
  - Leaves of Twin Oaks (Box 25)
  - LeBlanc, André E. (reference: L’Emancipation) (Box 25)
  - LeBrun, John L. (reference: index to Catholic Worker) (Box 25)
  - Lee, Mark W. (reference: speeches of William D. Haywood) (Box 25)
  - Lee, Dustin (from ECW re: Affirmative Action) (Box 25)
  - Lee, Martha (reference: ecology movement, radical environmentalism) (Box 25)
  - Lee, Paul (Box 25)
  - Leeder, Elaine (reference: Rose Pesotta) (Box 25)
  - Leeds, Gertrude (reference: The Comintern) (Box 25)
  - Leekley, Brian (reference: general) (Box 25)
  - Left Bank Books (Box 25)
  - Leftward (Toronto, Canada) (Box 26)
  - Legg, W. Dorr (re: One Institute) (Box 26)
  - Leidecker, Eugene (Box 26)
  - Lemar International (re: subscription to Marijuana Review) (Box 26)
  - Lentz, Richard (reference: Martin Luther King, Jr.) (Box 26)
  - Leon, D. H. (reference: Benjamin Tucker; Joseph Ishill; American anarchists) (Box 26)
  - Lerner Publications Co. (reference: reproduction of photograph of Eugene Debs) (Box 26)
  - Lesbian Archive and Information Centre (London) (Box 26)
  - Lesbian Herstory Archives (re: newsletter subscription) (Box 26)
  - Lesbian Tide (Hollywood, CA) (Box 26)
  - Leuchtenburg, William (including telegram) (reference: Spanish Civil War) (Box 26)
  - Leutner, Robert W. (re: donation of Les Temps Nouveaux) (Box 26)
  - Levasseur, Richard L. (reference: birth dates of anarchists for 1984 calendar) (Box 26)
  - Levi, Steven C. (reference: George Hinton Henry; Alaska; LA Times bombing in 1910) (Box 26)
  - Leviathan Publications (Box 26)
  - Levitt, Linda (reference: Americans in the Spanish Civil War) (Box 26)
  - LeWarne, Charles P. (reference: communitarian experiments in western Washington) (Box 26)
  - Lewin, Edward B. (reference: Seattle General Strike of 1919) (Box 26)
  - Lewis, Evon (4 folders) (Box 26)
  - Lewis, Leona (Box 26)
  - Lewis, Muriel (Box 26)
  - Lewis, Steven L. (reference: lesbian and gay history of the 1920s and 1930s) (Box 26)
  - L’Homme Libre (France) (Box 26)
  - Lianios, George (Box 26)
  - LIB Shinjuku Center (Tokyo, Japan) (Box 26)
  - Liberated Librarians Newsletter (Philadelphia) (Box 26)
  - Liberation (London) (Box 26)
  - Liberation News Service (New York) (Box 26)
  - Liberation Support Movement (Canada) (Box 26)
  - Liberator, The (New York) (Box 26)
  - Liberman, Esther (reference: Alexander Berkman) (Box 26)
  - Liberman, Michael (reference: William Morris) (Box 26)
  - Libero International (Japan) (Box 26)
  - Libertäre Blätter (Zurich) (Box 26)
  - Libertarian (Devon, U.K.) (Box 26)
  - Libertarian, The (Wenonah, N.J.) (Box 26)
  - Libertarian Analysis (New York) (Box 26)
  - Libertarian Broadsides (Ralph Myles) (Box 26)
  - Libertarian Connection (Los Angeles) (Box 26)
  - Libertarian Forum (New York) (Box 26)
  - Libertarian League (re: Checklist of Anarchist Periodicals, 1965) (Box 26)
  - Libertarian Teacher (see Libertarian Education) (Leicester, England) (Box 26)
  - Liberté, La (Paris, France) (Box 27)
  - Liberty (Port Townsend, WA) (letter to editor from ECW) (Box 27)
  - Liberty (New York) (Box 26)
  - Library of Congress (Box 27)
  - Library of Michigan (re: offer of $ to Jo Labadie for his collection) (Box 27)
  - Library of Social History (reference: general) (Box 27)
  - Lichtenberg, Virgil L. (reference: socialism in Iowa; The Iowa Reform; George Davis Herron) (Box 27)
  - Lichtenstein, Peter M. (reference: producers’ or worker cooperatives in the U.S.) (Box 27)
  - Lidtke, Vernon (reference: German socialists in 19th and early 20th centuries; essay on Labadie holdings) (Box 27)
  - Life Line (Dallas, TX) (Box 27)
  - Light & Flower Co. (distributors of underground newspapers) (Box 27)
  - Lindsey, Barbara (reference: Detroit uprising) (Box 27)
  - Linden Lane Magazine (Princeton, NJ) (Box 27)
  - Linzer, Elliott (re: donation of radical literature via Paul Avrich) (Box 27)
  - Lipton, Arthur (Box 27)
  - Liptzin, Stanley (reference: Ferrer Modern School, Stelton) (Box 27)
  - List, David (reference: IWW antiwar activities in Great Lakes region) (Box 27)
  - Little Free Press (Box 27)
  - Littlefield, Warren (re: NBC radio plays of 1939-1940; funny reply from ECW) (Box 27)
  - Loader, Jayne (Workers International Relief) (Box 27)
  - Lobster (Hull, UK) (Box 27)
  - Loew-Tatelbaum, Brenda (re: donation) (Box 27)
  - Logan, Maurice (reference: Labadie family genealogy) (Box 27)
  - Logos (Montreal) (Box 27)